{
	"questions_and_answers": [
		{
			"question": "What is the vision of Institute-Industry Collaboration?",
			"answer": "NMAMIT to be the centre of excellence for Institute-Industry Collaboration in India"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the mission of Institute-Industry Collaboration?",
			"answer": "To make NMAMIT a pivotal node in the diverse sets of industrial activities"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the pramble of Institute-Industry Collaboration?",
			"answer": "The details of collaboration with industries are important to know how far the engineering institutions have been successful in providing demand-based, industry-responsive education, how well the institutions are equipped to produce talent to meet market requirements and the extent to which they are connected with the industry to get inputs on future challenges in the market."
		},
		{
			"question": "Who is the director of Institute-Industry Collaboration?",
			"answer": "Prof. A.N. PARAMESWARAN is the director of Institute-Industry Collaboration"
		},
		{
			"question": "Who is the ADJUNCT FACULTY of Institute-Industry Collaboration?",
			"answer": "Mr. S. GOPINATH is the ADJUNCT FACULTY of Institute-Industry Collaboration"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is INITIATIVE MISSION 360?",
			"answer": "Institute-Industry Collaboration is a complex process, it requires dedicated efforts to establish a system to synergy the various stakeholders of the institution.\nFor further details, click on the link: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/iic-initiative-mission.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Is there any Industry Powered Automotive Learning Factory?",
			"answer": "Yes, there is.\nFor further details, click on the link: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/iic-power.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Is there any INDUSTRY SUPPORTED ACTIVE LEARNING LABORATORY?",
			"answer": "Yes, there is.\nFor further details, click on the link: https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/iic-industry-supported-active.php"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which department's undergraduate students were selected for final year project work at Hyundai Motor India Limited in June-July 2017?",
			"answer": "The undergraduate students from the Department of Mechanical Engineering of NMAM Institute of Technology were selected."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the significance of this opportunity for the students?",
			"answer": "It is prestigious for the students to receive projects from renowned car makers like Hyundai, providing them with industry-ready skills and firsthand exposure from Hyundai's project teams."
		},
		{
			"question": "When did the students carry out their final year project work at Hyundai Motor India Limited?",
			"answer": "They carried out their final year project work during June-July 2017."
		},
		{
			"question": "Which plant of Hyundai Motor India Limited did the students work at?",
			"answer": "The students worked at the Chennai plant of Hyundai Motor India Limited."
		},
		{
			"question": "Which Organizations are in Collaboration With NMAMIT?",
			"answer": "Please visit for detailed information\nhttps://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/iic-details.php"
		}
	]
}
